treato.com 2017-07-09

# Treato - Privacy Policy

Last modified: May 3, 2016 

This Privacy Policy (this Policy) manifests Treato's commitment to privacy. This Policy is incorporated into, subject to and a part of the Website's Terms of Use. If you do not agree to this Policy, you may not and should not use the Website. The definitions in the Website's Terms of Use apply to this Policy unless stated otherwise. 

Information Provided by Users

When you register with the Website we request for your e-mail and your chosen user name and password and we may store this information. We do not disclose any personally identifiable information (including any identifiable health information) provided by you as a registered user that you do not make publicly available on treato.com without your authorization. We do not disclose to any third-party any personally identifiable information (including any identifiable health information) provided by you as a registered user that you do not make publicly available on treato.com without your authorization, unless required by law. However, we reserve the right to notify public health authorities, law enforcement, or other persons capable of addressing the situation if we believe that such information (by itself or when coupled with information contained in any of your posts) indicates potential harm to yourself or others. 

Logs and Cookies

As most sites do, our systems may automatically record and store technical information regarding the method and nature of your use of the Website including your search history, favorite pages, pages which were tagged as 'Interesting' by you, posts you read, Google query that led to the Website, exit point, use time, IP, platform type, operating system information, number of clicks, browser information and relevant cookies. 

Our systems may automatically send cookies and other programs designed to gather non-personally identifiable information (information which does not and cannot be attributed to a specific user) ("Cookies") to your computer. We may store information which correlates with those Cookies, and designed to improve and optimize the Website. You may block and remove our Cookies through your browser and operating system, but this may impair and hinder the Website functionality and availability. Currently we are using Google Analytics to analyze the audience of the website and improve our content. As part of this effort, we are also using Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to better understand our audience and improve the site to meet it needs. No personal information is collect from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please visit:   
<http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>   
Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the  
In addition to Google Analytics, we are using other tools that help us the audience of the website and improve our content. These trackers are listed below accompanied with their relevant privacy policy:  
Click Tale (<http://www.clicktale.com/privacy-policy>)   
Alexa (<http://www.alexa.com/help/privacy>)   
DoubleClick by Google (<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>)   
Quantcast (<https://www.quantcast.com/how-we-do-it/consumer-choice/privacy-policy/>) 

Use of Information

We may use the gathered and stored information to improve quality and design of the Website, including without limitation, saving you the trouble of re-entering data and quarries, personalize and customize the Website, track your use of the Website and generate statistics regarding the Website. We may not disclose any personally identifiable information (including e-mail and user names) to any third party, except for the purpose of maintaining, operating, providing or improving the Website, including by sending you non-marketing, administrative or customer service e-mail messages. We may disclose aggregated non-personally identifiable statistical information to third parties, including without limitation pharma companies and the FDA. Note that your behavior on other websites may be tracked by Treato. 

Deleting your Information

If you wish to delete all information regarding your use of the Website, please contact us through [this form](http://treato.com/apps/pharma/contact.htm). 

No Obligation to Store Information

Nothing in this Policy is interpreted as an obligation to store information, and we may, at our own discretion, delete or avoid from recording and storing any and all information. We may store information in locations outside our direct control. 

Non-Restricted Information Disclosure

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary stated herein, we may: 

  * Disclose any information if we are required to do so by law or to aid a law enforcement agency in the prevention of a crime; 
  * Disclose any information in good faith and to the minimum extent required in legal proceedings to which we are a party, including without limitation, proceedings initiated by us; 
  * Disclose any information in good faith and to the minimum extent required to third parties who are requested by us to investigate allegations made against us, to protect the data security, integrity and/or operability of the Website, to protect our rights or to help prevent the occurrence of major harm to a person. 

Third Party Advertisements

We may use advertisements to fund the Website, which are placed, served, managed, operated and distributed by third parties (specialized ad industry companies) within the Website. Aside from non-identifiable information given to them, these third party companies use designated technologies (including cookies) which are not under our control or knowledge, in order to measure, improve and personalize their ad activity and effectiveness. 

Data Security

We place great emphasis on the security and integrity of your information and the data stored in our systems. The Website is provided under the best commercially reasonable data security practices, in order to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or deletion of any and all information stored in our systems. You acknowledge, however, that no such effort can completely guarantee the security of the stored data, that breaches of security are still a possibility both regarding our systems and that a data security breach resulting in unauthorized access to your information can occur in third party system (for example, ISP's and hosting services providers). As a result, we do NOT warrant or ensure the integrity and security of the data stored in its systems, including without limitation your information. 

Sign up using Social Networks

Facebook - When you login to Treato using Facebook, depending upon your privacy settings in Facebook, your friends and Facebook may be able to see automatically certain interactions with our site. By clicking “Sign in with facebook” or “Sign up with facebook”, you agree to share your interactions with Treato with Facebook and your Facebook friends. Treato is not responsible for your privacy settings on Facebook. 

Change of Ownership

In the event of a change of ownership or control of all or part of the Website, including without limitation through acquisition, merger or sale, we reserve the right to sell all or part of the personal information it stores in its systems. You acknowledge that in the event of bankruptcy, insolvency or receivership, we may have no control over the use and transfer of your personal information. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Policy may be revised from time to time at our sole discretion. The last revision will be reflected in the "Last modified" heading above. Please visit this page periodically for updates. Continuing to use the Website continues your acceptance of changes.
